when creating presentations it's always
a good idea to plan out the layout of
the presentation before you actually
come to create it so as you can see I
have the content on a Word document
which I wish to transfer into the
presentation this may be a document
that's been created by you or it may be
a document that's being provided by
someone else in your organization so as
you can see I need to transfer this text
it's set out in such area so I'm quite
clear as to what needs to go where so
I've got the tail slide which is slide 1
slide 2 slide 3 and slate for and in
this video I'm just going to quickly
demonstrate how you can add the text to
the slate so as you can see I've created
a new slide show and it automatically
starts with the slide 1 which will be
the tail of flight so I need to copy the
information from the word document and
place it into the presentation now I'm
going to copy the content for the tail
slate and highlight the text I want to
copy and then select the copy icon or I
can just use the ctrl + C shortcut once
it's highlighted go to the presentation
click where I want to paste it and
select control + V which will pierce the
text into the slate I can then select
the subheading for that slate again ctrl
+ C players thought into the subheading
box ctrl + V and that is out of that at
the moment I'm not too concerned with
the for Martin in the Leo that's what
everything like that will be dealt with
it later on and so now I need that I'd
Slade - so I've got a slate - new Slade
and I want a Slade which is a tail and
content and I will then copy the title
for Slade - piece of into the tail box
on Slate - and then the content for
Slade to copy that and then place that
into the box at the moment as I see I'm
not too concerned it's added a bullet
point but I won't want that so I will
tear that are we later on and then again
another new slide which is tailing
content copy the subheading not the
heading sorry and then the main body of
text that see the slate and then finally
another new slide title and content copy
appears to be heading for that slate and
then the content so there as you can see
I've now added the content for all four
of the slate so I'm ready to start
making changes into the layout in the
structure